Justice League: Crisis on Infinite Earths Part Three is a animation,
science fiction, action film directed by Jeff Wamester.
Now fully revealed as the ultimate threat to existence, the Anti-Monitor wages an unrelenting
attack on the surviving Earths that struggle for survival in a pocket universe.
One by one, these worlds and all their inhabitants are vaporized!
On the planets that remain, even time itself is shattered, and heroes from the past join
the Justice League and their rag-tag allies against the epitome of evil.
But as they make their last stand, will the sacrifice of
the superheroes be enough to save us all?
Batman / Bruce Wayne (voice), played by Jensen Ackles.
Superman / Earth-2 Superman (voice), played by Darren Criss.
Lex Luthor (voice), played by Corey Stoll.
Batgirl (voice), played by Gideon Adlon.
Martian Manhunter / J'onn J'onzz (voice), played by Ike Amadi.
Psycho Pirate / Charles Halstead (voice), played by Geoffrey Arend.
Justice League: Crisis on Infinite Earths is a 2024 American animated superhero film trilogy featuring the DC Comics superhero team the Justice
League and based on the DC Comics storyline Crisis on Infinite Earths (1985–1986) written by Marv Wolfman and pencilled by George Pérez.
The films were directed by Jeff Wamester from a script by Jim Krieg.
They are the 54th, 55th, and 56th films of the DC
Universe Animated Original Movies.
They are the eighth, ninth, and tenth (and final) installments in the second phase of the DC
Animated Movie Universe, as well as the 23rd, 24th, and 25th (and final) films overall.
Justice League: Crisis on Infinite Earths – Part
One was released on January 9, 2024.
Part Two was released on April 23, and Part Three was released on July 16.
The films were dedicated to comic artist George Pérez who died on May 6, 2022, and
longtime Batman actor Kevin Conroy who died later that same year on November 10.
The film explores themes of superhero, end of the world, based on
graphic novel, superhero team, parallel universe.
The tone is thought_provoking.